makersrow.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Maker’s Row - Factory Sourcing Made Easy

_Last Updated: October 22, 2012_

At Maker’s Row, Inc. (“Maker’s Row”), we value your privacy. This Privacy Notice describes what information we collect from users of the Maker’s Row Website (“Site” or “makersrow.com”), how we use that information, and how we disclose that information. By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of personal information in accordance with this policy. By using the Site, you also agree to be bound by the Maker’s Row Terms and Conditions (“Terms”), as set forth here.

BY USING OUR SITE OR SERVICES OR SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION THROUGH OUR SITE OR SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT AND YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION ACCORDING TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICE. IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF TO BE USED IN THE MANNER SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY NOTICE, DO NOT USE THE SITE.

Our mission is to make American manufacturing accessible. Whether you’re a company or individual, we are providing unparalleled access to large and small factories in the USA.

#### 1\. What Information Do We Collect?

_Passive Information We Collect About You_

When you visit makersrow.com, some information is automatically collected, such as your IP address, browser type, system type, the content and pages that you access on the Site, the “referring URL” (i.e., the page from which you navigated to makersrow.com), the pages you navigate to on the Site, and from which you leave the Site, as well as the time you spend on the Site. In addition to using Uniform Resource Locators (URL), we also use Cookies to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the information for which you searched and viewed.

We use cookies to collect additional website usage data, and to improve and personalize the Site and our service to you. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk.

We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our services. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

We collect information passively using technologies such as standard server logs, cookies, and clear GIFs (also known as “Web beacons”). We use passively-collected information to administer, operate, and improve makersrow.com and our other services and systems, and to provide services and content that are tailored to you. We may aggregate information collected from our users to show statistical data to our potential investors. WE WILL NOT SHARE, SELL, RENT, SWAP OR OTHERWISE AUTHORIZE ANY THIRD PARTY TO ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

Also, please be aware that third parties may set cookies on your hard drive or use other means of collecting information about your use of their services or content. We do not have access to, or control over, these third-party means of passive data collection and do not assume responsibility for such third-party privacy practices.

_Personal Information We Collect From You_

We may also collect personal information from you, specifically information that you provide to us when you create your factory profile or user account. For instance, when you register on the Site, request information about products or services, request support, or otherwise communicate with us, we collect the personal information that is provided to us. We may collect personal information such as name, e-mail address, city, state, country, other demographic information, interests and preferences, company information, payment information, and any other information you choose to share in your profile. For example, when a user registers for our site, we collect the user’s name and email address. Personal information may also include information about an individual’s activities, such as, without limitation, information about his or her activity on the Site.

Please note that in order to fulfill your requests for paid services (e.g., Factory Member Services, as defined in the Terms); we share your payment information with our payment processor.

#### 2\. How We Use Your Information

_Personally Identifiable Information_

We do not use personal information collected from you in a personally identifiable manner. We may aggregate the personal information collected from our users in a non-personally identifiable manner. Aggregate information is information that we collect about a group or category of products, services or customers that is not personally identifiable or from which individual identities are removed. WE MAY USE AND DISCLOSE AGGREGATE INFORMATION, AND OTHER NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, FOR VARIOUS PURPOSES. WE WILL NOT SHARE, SELL, RENT, SWAP OR OTHERWISE AUTHORIZE ANY THIRD PARTY TO ACCESS YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION.

_Using Your Information to Aggregate Statistics_

We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, the Site and e-mails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user. We may also use non-personally identifiable aggregate statistics of our users for internal purposes such as to administer, operate and improve the Site.

We may provide your information to third-party services who work on behalf of or with us to provide some of the services and features of the Site or services and to help us communicate with you. Examples of such services may include, but are not limited to, sending emails, analyzing data, and providing marketing assistance. These third-parties are required not to disclose your personal information and not to use your personal information except based on our instructions and in accordance with this Privacy Notice. Any information we disclose or use will be in non-personally identifiable form.

_Disclosing Your Information as a Part of a Merger, Sale or Other Financing_

In the event of a change in ownership, or a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to, another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of your personal information to that entity. Information about our users, including personal information, may be disclosed and/or sold as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, or similar transaction by us, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information could be transferred and/or sold to third parties as one of our business assets.

_Using Your Information to Improve Maker’s Row_

We may also use personal information to provide services and information that you request; to enhance, improve, operate, and maintain makersrow.com, our programs, services, website, and other systems; to prevent fraudulent use of the Site and services; to tailor your user experience; to maintain a record of our dealings with you, and for other administrative purposes.

_Disclosing Your Information if Legally Required_

We may also disclose personal information if we believe that doing so is legally required or is in our interest to protect our property or other legal rights (including, but not limited to, enforcement of our agreements), or the rights or property of others.

_Feedback_

If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your personal information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the personal information in it in accordance with this Privacy Notice.

#### 3\. Third Party Sites & Affiliates

The Site may contain links to other websites. Maker’s Row is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. This Privacy Notice applies solely to information collected by us through the Site or services and does not apply to these third party websites. Users will need to check the privacy policies of these others websites to understand their policies. Users who access a linked site may be disclosing their personal information.

#### 4\. Opt Out

Users may e-mail the Site administrator at [tanya@makersrow.com](mailto:tanya@makersrow.com) to remove user information from our database if they so desire.

#### 5\. Age Restrictions

The Site is not directed to children and children are not eligible to use our Site or services. We do not collect or maintain personal information from people we actually know are under 13 years old, and no part of the Site or services is designed to attract people under 13 years old. If we later obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 13 years old, we will take steps to remove that user's personal information from our databases.

Our Site and services are intended for users and visitors over the age of 18. It is our policy that visitors and users of our Site who are between the ages of 13 and 18 do so only with consent of a parent or guardian.

If you are under the age of 18 and have already provided personal information through the site without consent from a parent or guardian, please have your parent or guardian contact us immediately, so that we can remove such information from our files. Your parent or guardian may contact us at [tanya@makersrow.com](mailto:tanya@makersrow.com).

#### 6\. International Visitors

Maker’s Row is hosted in the United States and is generally intended for United States visitors. If you visit from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please be aware that you are transferring personal information to the United States. The United States does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and some other regions. By providing personal information to us, you consent to the transfer of personal information to the United States and the use of personal information in accordance with this Privacy Notice.

#### 7\. Security

We use reasonable security measures that are designed to protect personal information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please note, however, that no data security measures can be guaranteed to be completely effective. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal information or other information. You transmit personal information to us at your own risk.

#### 8\. Updates to This Policy

We may occasionally update this Privacy Notice. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of the Privacy Notice. Your continued use of the Site after such changes will be subject to the then-current Privacy Notice. Notice of material changes will be posted on the Site's homepage and/or will be provided by e-mailing you or notifying you upon login about these changes; the form of such notice is up to our discretion. However, we encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Notice to stay informed about how we collect, use, and disclose personal information.

#### 9\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Notice, email us at [tanya@makersrow.com](mailto:tanya@makersrow.com).
